can I change my source and Target scheme
in between the tenure
see there are three main steps that you
need to complete when starting
freedomship one needs to carefully
choose the scheme for investment choose
the Sip amount and lastly choose the
number of years from the options
available
once the freedomship is registered with
all these details you are not allowed to
change the source scheme or the target
scheme but can I increase or decrease
the tenure
decreasing or increasing your tenure is
not allowed once your freedomship is
registered however as an alternative you
can always register a new freedomship
with your preferred tenure hope that
clarifies your doubt
mutual fund Investments are subject to
Market risks read all scheme related
documents carefully